proranktracker.com 2018-09-11

# Privacy Policy - Pro Rank Tracker

## Privacy Policy  
Effective date: 24th of May 2018

Pro Rank Tracker having a mailing address at P.O. Box 22602, Tel Aviv 61226, Israel (“we”, “our, “us”, “Company”) collects from the individual user (“you” or “your”) certain personal data through the website [http://proranktracker.com](http://proranktracker.com/) (“Website”).

This Privacy Policy contains our policies and procedures governing the collection and processing (i.e., storage, erasure, use, and disclosure) of personal data (i.e., any information relating to a natural person who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by using such information). This Privacy Policy applies only to the Website. It does not apply to any other websites owned and operated by third parties.

#### 1\. Personal data collected by us

We comply with data minimization principles and we collect only a minimal amount of personal data that is necessary for ensuring your use of the Website:

  * When you visit the Website, we collect your IP address.
  * When you complete an order form available on the Website, we collect your: (1) first and second name; (2) company name; (3) email address; (4) physical address; (5) phone number; (6) VAT number; (7) password; and (8) payment details (PayPal account or credit card number).
  * When you contact us through the contact form available on the Website, we collect your: (1) name; (2) email address; (3) phone number; and (4) any other information that you decide to provide us in your message.

**Sensitive data**. We do not collect, under any circumstances, any sensitive data from you, such as your health information, opinion about your religious and political beliefs, racial origins, membership of a professional or trade association, or information about your sexual orientation.

#### 2\. Non-personal data collected by us

When you visit the Website, we may automatically collect non-personal analytics data, such as information related to keywords tracked through the Website, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of websites clicked to and from the Website, pages views, and the average time spent on the Website. The non-personal data collected by us will be de-personalized and will not allow the identification of individuals in any manner.

**Aggregated data.** In case your non-personal data is combined with certain elements of your personal data in a way that allows us to identify you, we will treat such aggregated data as personal data.

#### 3\. The purpose of collection of personal data

We respect strictest data protection principles. Thus, we collect and process your personal data only for specified, explicit, and legitimate purposes.

We use your personal data to: (1) process your orders; (2) provide you with the requested services; (3) reply to your requests and questions; (4) analyze and improve our business activities; (5) optimize and improve the Website; and (6) deliver you our newsletter (if you have subscribed to one).

We also use your personal data to the extent necessary to enforce this Privacy Policy and to prevent imminent harm to persons or property. Moreover, we may use aggregated data for industry research and academic research.

#### 4\. The purpose of collection of non-personal data

We collect the non-personal data mentioned in Section 2 in order to analyze the keywords tracked through the Website and create statistics of such keywords. In addition, we collect the non-personal data to analyze what kind of users visit the Website, how they find it, how long they stay, from which other websites they come to the Website, what pages they look at, to which other websites they go from the Website.

#### 5\. Legal grounds for processing of personal data

Depending on the circumstances in which you provide us with your personal data, the collection and processing of your personal data is carried out on the basis of one of the following legal grounds:

  * Ensuring the performance of a contract;
  * Pursuing our legitimate business interests; or
  * If you have provided us with your explicit consent for collection and processing of your personal data for a particular purpose.

#### 6\. Marketing communication

We will send you direct marketing messages, including newsletters, promotions, and brochures, only if you provide us with your prior explicit consent to receive such marketing messages.

**Opt-out from marketing communication.** If you have provided us with your consent to receive direct marketing communication and, at some point, you would like to stop receiving such marketing messages, you can easily opt-out by:

  * Clicking on the “unsubscribe” link contained in any of the online marketing communications submitted to you; or
  * Contacting us directly by email at .

**Informational notices.** Please note that the following informational notices sent by us on an “if-needed” basis do not fall within the scope of direct marketing communication that requires your explicit consent: (1) information about your user account and the services used by you; (2) information about our new services that are closely related to the services already used by you; and (3) informational notices regarding updates of the Website, your privacy and security, and other important matters.

#### 7\. Merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets

If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, the Company reserves the right to transfer personal and non-personal data to a party involved in the merger, acquisition or sale, to the extent such information is necessary to carry out the merger, acquisition or sale.

#### 8\. Protection of personal data

We employ organizational and technical information security measures to protect your personal data, including limited access to your personal data by our staff, Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”), firewalls, and secure server facilities. SSL is a protocol for encrypting information over the Internet.

However, due to the inherent risks of using the Internet, we cannot be liable for any unlawful destruction, loss, use, copying, modification, leakage, and falsification of your personal data caused by circumstances beyond our reasonable control. In case a personal data breach occurs, we will inform the relevant data protection authority without undue delay and immediately take reasonable measures to mitigate the breach, as stipulated in the applicable law.

#### 9\. Third party access to personal data

Where necessary, we may disclose your personal data to third parties. Such a disclosure is limited to the situations when the personal data is required for the following purposes:

  * Ensuring the operation of the Website;
  * Ensuring the processing and completion of your orders;
  * Pursuing our legitimate business interests;
  * Carrying out our contractual obligations;
  * Law enforcement purposes; or
  * If you provide your prior explicit consent.

Your personal data may be disclosed to third parties that provide professional, technical, and other types of support to us, including our: (1) independent contractors; (2) web developing partners; (3) hosting and data storage providers; (4) user information logistics providers; (5) mailing service providers; (6) chat provider; and (7) payment service providers.

The third parties listed in this section 9 will access your personal data as a part of their partnership with us and only if they agree to ensure an adequate level of protection of personal data that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

#### 10\. Transfer of personal data outside the EEA

Please note that some third parties listed in Section 9 of this Privacy Policy may be located outside the EEA and, if you are a resident of the EEA, we may need to transfer your personal data to jurisdictions outside the EEA. In case it is necessary to make such a transfer, we will make sure that the jurisdiction in which the recipient third party is located ensures an adequate level of protection of your personal data or we conclude an agreement with the respective third party that ensures such protection.

#### 11\. Your rights regarding your personal data

You can manage your personal data collected and processed by us and request us to:

  * Get a copy of your personal data that we store;
  * Move your personal data to another processor;
  * Delete your personal data from our systems;
  * Object and restrict processing of your personal data;
  * Withdraw your consent; or
  * Process your complaint.

If you would like to exercise your rights, please contact us by email at . We may ask you to provide us with an identifying piece of information, so that we would be able to identify you in our system. We will answer your request within a reasonable timeframe but no later than 2 weeks.

You can also edit your personal data through your user account on the Website.

**Launching a complaint.** If you would like to launch a complaint about the way in which your personal data is handled by us, we kindly ask you to contact us first. After you contact us, we will investigate your complaint and provide you with our response as soon as possible. If you are a resident of the EU and you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority.

**Children.** The Website cannot be accessed by persons under the age of 18. If a person under the age of 18 has provided us with personal data without obtaining parental or guardian consent in advance, the parent or guardian may contact us and request us to destroy the personal data.

#### 12\. Cookies

The Website uses cookies. This section 12 describes the types of cookies we use and indicates the purposes for which the cookies are used by us.

**What is a cookie?** A cookie is a small computer file, typically consisting of letters and numbers. When you visit a website, the website may send a cookie to your browser. Subsequently, the browser may store the cookie on your computer system. The main purpose of cookies is to allow a website to recognize user’s device. There are two types of cookies, namely, persistent cookies and session cookies. Persistent cookies remain valid until their expiration date, unless deleted by the user before that date. Session cookies will be stored on a web browser and will remain valid until the moment when the browser is closed.

**What cookies do we use cookies?** We use the following types of cookies:

  * Session cookies, such as [ _PRT, WHMCS_ ];
  * Persistent cookies, such as [ _PRT, WHMCS_ ]; and
  * Third-party cookies, such as [ _GA, Zopim_ ].

**For what purposes do we use cookies?** We use session cookies to verify your details until you are navigating from page to page on the Website. The session cookies enable you to avoid re-entering your details each time you enter a new page on the Website. We use persistent cookies in order to recognize you as a unique user when you return to the Website. As a result, you do not have to enter your login details multiple times as you move from other websites to the Website. We may also serve you targeted advertisements on the basis of your pervious use of the Website and other websites online. We will not use cookies for purposes which are not mentioned in this Privacy Policy.

**How to disable cookies?** If you would like to refuse our use of cookies, you can do so by disabling cookies in your browser (please check your browser’s “help” functionality for more information) or visiting [http://www.whatarecookies.com](http://www.whatarecookies.com/) for further information. Please be aware that some parts of the Application may not function properly and some services may not be available without cookies.

**Google Analytics.** We use Google Analytics to analyze your use of the Website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information by means of cookies and we use its services to create reports about the use of the Website and to collect data via advertising cookies and identifiers. We use the following Google Analytics features: (i) Remarketing with Google Analytics; (ii) Google Display Network Impression Reporting; (iii) Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting; and (iv) Integrated services that require Google Analytics.

**Opting-out from Google Analytics.** If you would like to opt out from Google Analytics, you can do so by installing a Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en> .

#### 13\. Term, termination, and amendment 

This Privacy Policy enters into force on the effective date indicated at the top of the Privacy Policy and remains valid until terminated or updated by us. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version on the Website. The new version will become effective on the date it is posted.

#### 14\. Retention period

We will store your personal data in our systems only for as long as such personal data is required for the purposes indicated in Section 3 of this Privacy Policy. After your personal data is no longer necessary for such purposes, we will immediately delete your personal data from our systems. In some cases, we may be required by law to retain your personal data for a certain period of time (e.g., for maintaining our accountancy records). In such cases, we will store your personal data for the time period stipulated by the applicable law.

#### 15\. Your consent

By using the Website, you are consenting to our processing of your personal data as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us.

In exceptional cases (where required by the applicable law), we will seek your explicit consent. For example, we may seek your explicit prior consent for the following purposes:

  * If we would like to provide you with any marketing communication (e.g., sending you a newsletter);
  * If we intend to use your personal data for the purposes that are not indicated in this Privacy Policy;
  * If we would like to disclose or transfer your personal data to third parties that are not indicated in this Privacy Policy;
  * If we intend to collect any sensitive data from you; or
  * If we significantly amend this Privacy Policy. 

#### 16\. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please send us a message by using the online form available at <https://proranktracker.com/members/submitticket.php>, or please write to the following mailing address:

Pro Rank Tracker  
P.O. Box 22602  
Tel Aviv 61226  
Israel

#### 17\. Last amendment

This Privacy Policy has been last amended on 24th of May 2018.
